virginmobilefeed.com 2015-09-29

# Virgin Mobile USA Privacy Policy

#### Effective date: August 4, 2014

IMPORTANT NOTICE: Our privacy policy has been updated to reflect that Virgin Mobile USA will be introducing two new programs: 1) Mobile Advertising - which allows Virgin Mobile USA to use information it collects to provide service to you to make the ads you see on your device more relevant (You must opt in to this program) and 2) Reporting & Analytics - to create and share certain business and marketing reports (You may opt out of this program.). We will not share any information that identifies you personally under either of these new programs. For detailed information on these programs and to learn how to opt in or out, please visit virginmobileusa.com/privacy. 

PLEASE NOTE: Assurance Wireless customers are not included in these programs   

### VIRGIN MOBILE USA PRIVACY POLICY

This Privacy Policy ("Policy") describes how Virgin Mobile USA, L.P. ("Virgin Mobile", or "we", "us", "our") will collect, access, use or disclose your personal information. It applies to all of our products, services and websites ("Services"). A few of our Services may be covered by different privacy policies and in the event of a conflict between the two, the product or service specific policy governs. Our collection, use, access, disclosure and safeguarding of your personal information is subject to U.S. law. 

INFORMATION COLLECTED   
USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION   
INFORMATION WE SHARE   
NETWORK AND INFORMATION SECURITY   
CHILDREN   
INFORMATION CHOICES AND CHANGES   
CONTACTING US   
UPDATING THIS POLICY   
YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

#### Information Collected

We collect personal information about you in various ways. We may also get information from other sources and may combine it with information we collect about you. Personal information is information that identifies or is associated with a specific person, such as a name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, or information about activities directly linked to that person. Personal information does not include information that is not used to identify you, including aggregate or anonymous information. 

Information you give us: You may give us information in a variety of ways, including when you sign up for or use Virgin Mobile Services, communicate with customer care or register on one of our websites. For example, you may provide us information such as our name, billing address, telephone number ore-mail address. We also collect information about your demographics, activities, location and personal preferences. Third-party providers, whose sites are featured on and accessed via our website, may collect information as well. Such collection and use of your information is governed by the third party's privacy policy - not by this one. 

If we have trouble processing your order, the contact information you provide is used to get in touch with you. We also use this contact information to provide you with updates regarding your current phone or service and to provide you with information about Virgin Mobile promotions and special offers. 

Virgin Mobile may offer the opportunity to participate in contests, giveaways, or other similar promotions we sponsor. Except as explained otherwise in the rules for a particular contest, giveaway, or promotion, any personal information you provide will be used in accordance with this Policy. 

Information we automatically collect: We automatically receive certain types of information whenever you use our Services. We may collect information about your device such as the type, version of operating system, signal strength, whether it is on and how it is functioning, as well as information about how you use the device and services available through it, such as your call and data usage and history, your location, web sites you have visited, applications purchased, downloaded or used and other similar information. We may link information we collect with personal information, such as information you give us at registration and check out. We may use systems or tools to follow your use of our Services and other applications, including using cookies, web beacons and other mechanisms, along with analysis of network and device information. For example, we allow collection by analytic service provider(s) of site click-stream and cookie data to help us track aggregate and individual use of our Services. We sometimes use cookies to enable features on our sites, such as the ability to save your shopping cart or set preferences. Advertisers and ad networks that serve ads on our sites may also use their own mechanisms, including cookies. These third party cookies or tools are governed by the privacy policies of the entities placing the ads and not by this policy. 

Information from other sources: We may obtain information about you from outside sources and add it to or combine it with your account information. For example, we often receive information from the retailer from whom you purchased your Virgin Mobile phone or device prior to initiating service with us. We also may use commercially available demographic and marketing information from third parties to help us better serve you or inform you about products or services that we think will be of interest to you. 

Back to Top

#### Virgin Mobile USA's Use of Personal Information

We use personal information for a variety of purposes, including providing you with Services. We use your personal information to do things like: 

  * Process your orders.
  * Protect our rights and property and those of our customers.
  * Respond to legal process and emergencies.
  * Develop or inform you of new products and services.
  * Anonymize or aggregate personal information for various purposes like market analysis or traffic flow analysis and reporting.
  * Monitor, evaluate or improve our products, Services, systems or networks.
  * Customize or personalize your experience with our Services.
  * Customize or personalize online advertising to bring you information about products and services of Virgin Mobile or others that may interest you, including co-branded offers.
  * Tell you about products or services from Virgin Mobile or others that better meet your needs. More specifically, and as permitted by law, Virgin Mobile may use e-mail, telemarketing, direct mail and wireless messages to inform you about products or services we think will interest you.

Back to Top

Information about our customers is one of our most important business assets, and therefore we strive to protect it and keep it confidential. We do not share information that identifies you personally with third parties other than as follows: 

Affiliates. We may share personal and non-personal information with affiliated entities for approved business purposes. 

Virgin Mobile USA's Service Providers. We may share personal information with third parties who perform services on our behalf. 

Group Account Holders. We offer group accounts to business and government customers, family customers and other group account holders ("Group Accounts"). The account holder for Group Accounts is the entity or person that buys the service or product for its employees, family members or other authorized users. You (as the user of a device) may receive service, certain pricing, terms or other benefits through a Group Account with us. If so, we may share with that Group Account holder customer registration and other information related to your use of our services. 

Third Party Verification Services. We may share limited personal information (e.g., address, phone number) with non-Virgin Mobile entities to assist with identity verification, and to prevent fraud and identity theft. 

Other third parties with your consent. We may share information with other third parties with your consent. For example, you may agree to our sharing your information with other third parties to hear about their products and services. Use of the information you agree to share will be subject to those third parties' separate privacy policies. 

Disclosures to Third Party Application and Service Providers. You may choose to use services and products offered by third party providers through our Services or devices such as third party applications. When you leave our network you may also use mobile roaming services provided by third parties. Your use of such services and applications may result in these third parties collecting your personal information and obtaining information from Virgin Mobile, including location information (when applicable). You may also choose to give personal information directly to third parties when using our Services. In each case, personal information you give a third party will be subject to its terms, conditions and policies - not this policy. You should review a third party's privacy policy and terms of service before providing your information or using the service. 

Business Transfers. Personal information about you may be disclosed as part of any merger, acquisition, sale of company assets or transition of service to another provider. In the unlikely event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership, personal information may also be transferred as a business asset. 

Protection of Virgin Mobile and Others. We may access, monitor, use or disclose your personal information or communications to do things such as: 

  * comply with the law or respond to lawful requests or legal process;
  * protect the rights or property of us, our agents, members, our customers, and others including to enforce our agreements, policies and terms of use; 
  * respond to emergencies;
  * initiate, render, bill, and collect for services; or
  * facilitate or verify the appropriate calculation of taxes, fees, or other obligations due to a local, state, or federal government requirement; or determine eligibility for government benefits. 

We may share information that is de-identified or in an aggregated form that does not directly identify you. We share de-identified or aggregate information for purposes such as to: 

  * Conduct market or traffic flow analysis and reporting or produce or facilitate production by others of business and marketing reports to share with third parties. For example, we may aggregate customer information across a particular region and create a report showing that 10,000 subscribers from a given city visited a sports stadium. If you do not wish for us to use your information to produce de-identified and aggregated data sets in the reports we share with third parties, you may opt out at any time. See virginmobileusa.com/privacy for details. Assurance Wireless customers are not included in this program. 
  * With your opt-in consent only, customize or personalize advertising based on information we collect about your use of your wireless device in order to provide wireless service to you. For example, we may use information about your mobile web browsing or use of mobile applications to deliver advertisements tailored to your interests, and we may share de-identified information about your use of your device with third parties so that they can tailor advertising to your interests based on that information. To participate in this program, you must opt in. See virginmobileusa.com/privacy for details on how to do so. Assurance Wireless customers are not included in this program. 

Back to Top

#### Network and Information Security

We maintain a variety of physical, electronic and procedural safeguards. These safeguards help protect your personal information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. Be sure to use a strong account PIN to access your information on our websites and not one you use for other services. 

Back to Top

#### Children's Privacy

Virgin Mobile does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. You should also be aware that wireless devices and services purchased for family use may be used by children under 13 without the knowledge of Virgin Mobile. If that happens, any information collected from the usage will appear to be the personal information of the actual adult subscriber and treated as such under this Policy. 

If you have any questions about Virgin Mobile's policies around children's privacy, please contact Virgin Mobile Customer Care at 1-888-322-1122. 

Back to Top

#### Information Choices and Changes

We offer you choices regarding how we contact you for marketing-related communications and whether we use information regarding your online or mobile web activities for marketing purposes. We also offer you choices regarding the use of de-identified information to make ads you see on your mobile device more relevant and to produce or facilitate production of business and marketing reports shared with third parties. Visit to learn about your choices and how to register your privacy preferences with us. 

You may also let us know that you do not want us to contact you for marketing purposes. If you are a Virgin Mobile customer with a No Annual Contract account, to change your notification settings, or to change any of your personal information, click [here](https://www2.virginmobileusa.com/myaccount/home.do) to log in to your Virgin Mobile account and-go to the "My Account" page (then select Account Info and then Contact Info). 

If you are a Virgin Mobile customer with a Contract account, to change your notification settings, or to change any of your personal information call 1-888-322-1122. 

If you register a do-not-contact request, we still may contact you for non-promotional purposes, such as emails or wireless messages related to your account or our ongoing business relations. If you disable cookies on your Internet browser, you also may stop some collection and use of data when you visit our websites. If you would like to change certain Virgin Mobile account information, you may create an online account and manage your account online. For more information, visit [www.virginmobileusa.com](http://www.virginmobileusa.com/). 

Back to Top

#### Changes to This Privacy Policy

This privacy policy is subject to change. If we need to change our privacy policy at some point in the future, we'll post the new policy promptly. When we change the policy we will give notice by changing the date it was last updated or as required by law. By using virginmobileusa.com, you agree that your visit to our site abides by the information contained in our Visitor's Agreement and Acceptable Use Policy. 

Back to Top

#### Your California Privacy Rights

Virgin Mobile shares personal information between Virgin Mobile affiliates and marketing agents for marketing purposes. Virgin Mobile does not disclose customers' personal information to third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes without your consent. California residents may request the categories of personal information Virgin Mobile shared with its affiliates during the previous calendar year, if any. Written requests may be sent to the Office of Privacy - Legal Department, Virgin Mobile USA, P.O. Box 4600, Reston, VA 20195. Virgin Mobile will respond to these requests within 30 days. Requests that come to us by other means may result in a delayed response. 

Back to Top

#### Questions or Concerns

If you have any questions about, or complaints that concern, this Privacy Policy please click on the Customer Support tab or call Virgin Mobile Customer Care at 1-888-322-1122. If you prefer, you also may write us at Office of Privacy - Legal Department, Virgin Mobile USA, P.O. Box 4600, Reston, VA 20195. 

Back to Top

#### This Privacy Policy was last revised August 4, 2014.
